{
  "LevelId": 54,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 544,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BUMFUZZLES",
      "question": "playful term is used to describe feelings of confusion, bewilderment,"
    },
    {
      "id": 545,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "HYDRONYLIC",
      "question": "chemical reaction or process that involves the addition of water"
    },
    {
      "id": 546,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "FETICHIZED",
      "question": "In anthropology, what term is used to describe the practice of attributing magical or supernatural powers"
    },
    {
      "id": 547,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SQUEEZABLE",
      "question": "an object or material that can be compressed or deformed easily by applying pressure,"
    },
    {
      "id": 548,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SCHNOZZLES",
      "question": "informal term is often used to refer to a person's nose,"
    },
    {
      "id": 549,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "YARDMASTER",
      "question": "person who is in charge of overseeing and managing the operations of a railroad yard,"
    },
    {
      "id": 550,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "WAITSTAFFS",
      "question": "the group of individuals employed to serve customers in a restaurant,"
    },
    {
      "id": 551,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "KOLKHOZNIK",
      "question": "a member of a collective farm in the former Soviet Union,"
    },
    {
      "id": 552,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "COMMITMENT",
      "question": "describe a strong dedication or devotion to a cause, goal, relationship,"
    },
    {
      "id": 553,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "AQUAPHOBIC",
      "question": "a strong fear or aversion towards water,"
    },
    {
      "id": 554,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "FRIENDSHIP",
      "question": "a close and supportive relationship between individuals characterized by mutual trust, affection,"
    }
  ]
}